https://portal.tfionline.com/en/policies/privacy-policy

Last updated: May 25, 2018
Welcome to the TFI Online Privacy Policy. TFI Online is a series of community websites for members of The Family International. Many of our sites are open to the general public. This policy sets out how your personal information is managed if you’re a TFI Online member or visitor to our sites. This policy applies across all TFI Online sites (see the complete list of sites at the bottom of this page).
For members of TFI there is an additional privacy policy that covers members.tfionline.com and the personal information that you enter there.
Personal information we collect
We collect a very limited amount of personal information about visitors to TFI Online sites.
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit one of TFI’s websites ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
We use a third party service Google Analytics to collect, monitor and analyze anonymous statistical data to help us determine how to improve the TFI Online sites and services we provide. A randomized IP address is sent to Google Analytics for statistical purposes and does not uniquely identify you.
If you subscribe to one of our Email Subscriptions, we will collect your name and email address so that we can fulfill your subscription request. This personal information is transferred to our third party email service MailChimp and only used to deliver the requested subscription(s) to you. You can review MailChimp’s Privacy Policy here.
How we keep your personal information secure
Your personal information is stored on secure servers that are managed by TFI’s webmaster and
service providers. Any personal information that is stored or transmitted is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication and data encryption where appropriate.
How you can access your personal information
Every subscription email contains links near the top and bottom to “update preferences” and “unsubscribe”. You can use these links to change the subscription or to unsubscribe. Unsubscribing will completely erase your information.
If you would like to erase your information and are not able to use the “unsubscribe” link on an email, please notify us at subscriptions@tfionline.com and we will be happy to erase your information for you.
Cookies and web analytics
When you visit TFI websites, certain information is recorded that is generally anonymous information and does not reveal your identity, including:
your IP address or proxy server IP address (anonymized before sending to Google Analytics);
the domain name you requested;
the name of your internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;
the date and time of your visit to the website;
the length of your session;
the pages you have accessed;
the number of times you access the site within any month;
the file URL you view and information relating to it;
the website that referred you to TFI websites; and
the operating system your computer uses.
TFI’s websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). The information generated about your usage of
these websites will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will collect this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of TFI websites, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and to provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
Further information about Google’s privacy policy may be obtained from https://policies.google.com/privacy.
Contact us
If you have general questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@thefamilyinternational.com. For specific questions about email subscriptions, please contact us at subscriptions@tfionline.com.
TFI Online Websites
The following websites are all part of the TFI Online network, and as such are covered by TFI’s Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy.
The Children of God Photo Gallery: https://www.flickr.com/photos/146761602@N04/albums
The Family International: https://www.thefamilyinternational.org/
Virginia Brandt Berg: https://virginiabrandtberg.org/
Explore TFI online network
Looking for a new life?
Charter of the Family Internationalhttps://portal.tfionline.com/en/pages/charter/
TFI on Facebookhttps://www.facebook.com/thefamilyinternational
The Children of Godhttps://www.childrenofgod.com/
The Children of God Photo Galleryhttps://www.flickr.com/photos/146761602@N04/albums
The Family Internationalhttps://www.thefamilyinternational.org/
The Family International (Chinese)https://www.thefamilyinternational.org/zh/
The Family International (Europe)https://thefamilyeurope.org/
The Family International (French)https://www.thefamilyinternational.org/fr/
The Family International (Portuguese)https://www.thefamilyinternational.org/pt/
The Family International (Spanish)https://www.lafamilia.org/
Virginia Brandt Berghttps://virginiabrandtberg.org/
Copyright © 2020 The Family International
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
